…==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==…
更多精彩影视 请访问 http：//cmct.cc
影片压制：小鱼 字幕调校：小鱼 招募Q号：76846146
片名：人皮客栈
- 阿姆斯特丹 操 - 好了
- Amsterdam, motherfucker. - Okay.
快点 我们走 我们要去哪里？
Come on, let's go. Where are we going?
红灯区 找点乐子
Red-light district. Time for sneepur.
让我们先去喝杯咖啡然后再去猎艳
Let's go to the coffee shop first, then get some sneepur.
嘿 我想安妮之家博物馆就在这附近
Hey, I think the Anne Frank house is around here.
难道我们来欧洲 就是为了吸大麻？
Did we come to Europe just to smoke pot?
我大老远从冰岛跑过来
I came all the way from Iceland.
- 好吧 是又怎么样？- 我们在学校每天就是干这个
- Yeah, what if we did? - We did that every day in college.
为什么不 比如 去参观下博物馆？
Why not, like, you know, check out a museum?
你说的没错 我们是应该去一个博物馆
No, you're right. We should go to a museum.
大麻博物馆怎么样？
How about the hemp museum?
欧利隆重介绍
Oli proudly presents…
伊莎贝拉
lsabella.
她真可爱
She's cute.
但是我们不能接受 一个神智不清的女孩
But we can't rail a girl who's in a coma.
我想就算是在阿姆斯特丹 这也是违法的
I think that's illegal even in Amsterdam.
- 嘿 伙计们 这只是个热身 - 去他妈的欧利
- Hey, I'm just warming up, man. - Fucking Oli.
冰岛人 天啊 你怎么样？
The Icelandic Oh, God, how are you?
想飘飘欲仙么？
You want to get stoned?
- 这会使你兴奋 - 是什么？
- This will wake you up. - What the fuck?
这是上好的阿姆斯特丹毒品
This is good Amsterdam shit.
真有毒品在那里面 伙计
That's the shit right there, dude.
相信我
Trust me.
好
Yeah.
- 真不错 兄弟 - 没错 吸啊
- It's all good, bro. - Yeah, dude, smoke it!
- 伙计 怎么了？- 阿姆斯特丹就没有荷兰人吗？
- Dude, what happened? - Any Dutch people in Amsterdam?
嘿 这是我的朋友 乔希
All right, this is my friend, Josh.
- 哦 你好 - 你好
- Well, hello. - Hi.
- 你们想再找一个么？- 是的 好啊
- Do you guys want another round? - Yes, okay.
是吗？
Yeah?
我们马上回来
We will be right back.
- 你在干什么？- 怎么了？
- What are you doing? - What?
你见哪个人戴着一个这种破腰包？
Do you see a single other person in here with a fucking fanny pack?
等一下 那里有一个
Wait. There's a guy.
你为什么不过去 带着你的包包和他上床？
Why don't you go have fanny-pack sex with him…
然后在各自的腰包里射精？
and jizz all over each other's storage compartments?
我的口袋放不下护照 会磨我的大腿的
I can't put my passport in my pocket. It chafes my thighs, bitch.
- 行了吗？- 是的
- All right? - Yeah.
欧利呢？
Where's Oli?
他他妈的真是个天才
He's fucking genius.
激情提示 看正3点方位
Sneepur alert, 3 o'clock.
- 她抽烟 - 伙计 这里是欧洲
- She smokes. - Dude, it's Europe!
每个女孩儿都抽烟 别犯傻了
Every fucking chick smokes. Stop being a pussy.
你有时要求很低啊
You are so easy sometimes.
动力腰包归你了 我要过去了
The power of the pack is yours. I'm out of here.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
哦 我 不 别再和我说荷兰话
Yeah, I No, I don't even speak Dutch.
不 抱歉 我
No, I'm sorry, l…
离我远点 你这头蠢驴 滚远点
Get off me, you fucking faggot-ass elf. Fuck off.
- 嘿 怎么了？- 嘿 嘿
- Hey, what the fuck? - Hey. Hey.
来啊 蠢驴
Come on, faggot.
- 该死的！- 把你的脏手从我的身上拿开
- Fucker! - Get your fucking hands off me.
- 我是美国人 我有权利 - 快他妈滚蛋
- I'm an American, I got rights. - Get the fuck out.
你的俱乐部只配亲别人屁股 兄弟
Your fucking club sucks ass, bro.
亲吻我的美国屁股吧 该死的
Kiss my American ass, fucker.
- 去你妈的 - 我们走把 兄弟
- Fuck you. - Let's get out of here, bro.
嘿 我不知道你们 为什么还排队
Hey, I don't know why you guys are waiting.
这就像是个垃圾集中营 到处都是蠢驴
It's a fucking fag fest in there. Wall-to-wall fucking cock.
你需要这些中的一个才能进去 不好意思了 兄弟
You need one of these to get in, bro. Sorry.
那些大麻真是一流 伙计
That shit was classic, dude.
他差点和一个400磅的荷兰人同归于尽
He was gonna throw down with a 400-pound Dutchman.
我真威猛
I'm fucking awesome!
我不知道怎么了
I don't fucking know what…
我觉得你像个犹太人 伙计 那家伙就是该死的以色列人
I thought you were a Jew, man. This guy's a fucking Israeli!
你正在教训以色列人
You are fucking Israeli.
哦 天 我希望人兽性交在阿姆斯特丹是合法的
Oh, God, I hope bestiality is legal in Amsterdam…
那女孩真象头猪 看那边
because that girl's a fucking hog. Look at that, man.
嘿 伙计们 我觉得她喜欢我
Hey, guys, I think she likes me, man.
哦 看那边 乔希 这是我给你的礼物
Oh, look at that. Josh, my gift to you, man.
谢谢 但是让她做什么都得付钱
Thanks, but paying to do whatever you want to
这可一点都不刺激
someone isn't a turn-on.
不多点经验怎么能度过你的青春期呢？
How are you gonna get over your chick if you don't bang some new pussy?
你不能什么都不干就回家
You can't go home without getting some hot chick.
我同意 但是我不应该付钱
I agree, but I shouldn't have to pay for it.
嘿 快点 我埋单
Hey, come on, I'm paying, man.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你好？你好？
Hello? Hello?
嘿 关门 谁看谁付钱
Hey, close the door. You watch, you pay.
抱歉 上帝
Sorry. Jesus.
你完事了？小子
You're up, slugger.
恩 我他妈得太累了 几乎都爬不起来了
Man, I'm fucking… I'm tired, man. I can, like, barely stand up.
乔希 你想当作家对吗？
Josh, you want to be a fucking writer?
不如去那个房间多点人生经历如何？
How about some life experience, right there in that room.
- 这里边在干什么？- 嘿 看了就得付钱
- What do we have in here? - Hey, you watch, you pay.
我付 我付 来 快点
I pay. I pay, man. Come on.
嘿
Hey.
来 坐下
Come, sit.
你的朋友们很有趣
Your friends are so funny.
是的
Yeah.
你可以到这洗洗 在水池这里
You can wash over here, by sink.
真美妙啊
It was fine.
你什么意思？那个婊子有阿姆斯特丹最棒的乳房
What do you mean? That bitch had the best fucking tits in Amsterdam.
还好拉 就这么回事
It was fine. It was whatever.
怎么了？
What was that?
- 已经过了宵禁时间了 - 宵禁？我们多大了？13岁吗？
- It's fucking after curfew, man. - Curfew? What are we, 13?
让我们进去 快把我们的睾丸冻掉了
Let us the fuck in, we're freezing our balls off.
我们交了钱的 他们不能就这样把我们锁在外面
We paid to stay here. They can't just, like, lock us out.
真操蛋
This is bullshit.
你好？
Hello?
打开这该死的门
Open the fucking door.
- 你和他说什么？- 他只是告诉他们让我们进去
- What did you tell him? - He just told them to let us in.
- 闭嘴 - 上帝
- Shut up! - Jesus.
都他妈闭嘴 你们这群该死的美国人
Shut the fuck up, you fucking Americans.
嘿 我知道怎么做了
Hey, I know what to do.
闭嘴
Shut up.
嘿 嘿 伙计们 上来 快点爬
Hey, hey, guys. Up here. Climb quickly.
快点
Come on.
走
Go. Go, go, go.
哦 别理他们
Oh, don't mind them.
他们很混乱 都不知道自己在那颗星球上
They are so fucked up they don't know what planet they are on.
- 谢谢 兄弟 - 没关系
- Thanks, bro. - It's no problem.
并不是所有人都痛恨美国人的
Not everyone want to kill Americans.
帕克斯顿
Paxton.
艾里克西 但是你可以叫我艾里克斯
Alexei. But call me Alex.
那么 艾里克斯 这是乔希和欧利
What's up, Alex. This is Josh and Oli.
伙计们 真他妈的威猛
Guys, this is fucking awesome, man.
这是我第一次有找到乐子的机会
I'm the first in line for sneepur.
哦 那是冰岛话阴蒂的意思
Oh, that's Icelandic for "clit."
阴核或者阴蒂 你是想说这个意思吗
Clitoris or clitoris, however you wanna say that.
女人都有
Women have it.
好像在阴唇附近 像是悬挂起来的
It's, like, right near the labia. Like, it hangs.
哦 那你们在冰岛什么地方寻欢作乐
Oh, yeah. Very good sneepur in Iceland.
- 哦 - 快来 伙计们 坐下
- Yeah. - Come on, guys, have a seat.
你们去过哪里都？
Where you travel to?
我们从巴黎开始 在那里我们遇见了这个混混
We started in Paris, which is where we met this drifter.
总之 我们走遍法国
Anyway, we went all over France…
然后去了瑞士 比利时 现在我们在阿姆斯特丹
and then Switzerland, Belgium, and now we're in Amsterdam.
哦 阿姆斯特丹没多少 美国有很多
Yeah, kind of over Amsterdam. Way too many Americans.
是的 但是欧利有个朋友 在巴塞罗那有座公寓
Yeah, but Oli's got a friend with a flat in Barcelona…
他应该帮我们和那些辣妹联系
and he's supposed to hook us up with some hot-ass senoritas.
找女孩吗？
Looking for girls?
- 对 - 对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
所以告诉艾里克斯
So talk to Alex.
他干过全欧洲的女人
He open up the pussy all over the Europe.
我可以帮助你们
I can help you.
哦 该死的 埃里克斯显然是个拉皮条的
Oh, shit. Alex is a pimp, apparently.
谢谢 兄弟 但是我觉得我们自己能搞定
Thanks, bro, but I think we'll be okay.
- 对 - 好
- Yeah. - Good.
你们在找这样的女孩吗？
You looking for girls like this?
这些可真美妙
These are fucking magnificent.
- 这些该死的女孩是谁？- 你必须朝东走 我的朋友
- Who the hell are these girls? - You have to go east, my friend.
最好的女孩都在那里呢
This is where the best girls are.
最好的
The best.
向东多远？
How far east?
你们可以一直走到乌克兰 在敖德萨附近
You can go as far as Ukraine, around Odessa.
这些女孩是我在斯洛伐克的 一个客栈见到的
These girls I met at this one hostel in Slovakia…
就在布拉迪斯拉发城外
just outside Bratislava.
那些女孩都很辣 你都不能相信
The girls there are so hot you cannot believe it.
她们喜欢外国人 尤其是美国人
And they love anyone foreign, especially American.
她们听到你们的口音 肯定和你们干
They hear your accent, they fuck you.
等等 这个地方在布拉迪斯拉发附近吗？
So wait, this place is near Bratislava?
乔希
Josh.
任何旅行指南上都没有记载这个客栈
You won't find this hostel in any guidebook.
巴塞罗那 有这么多美国人
Barcelona, so many Americans.
但是斯洛伐克？一个美国人都没有
But Slovakia? No one there.
那里又很多女人 因为战争 却没有男人
There is so much pussy, and because of the war, there are no guys.
你去了那个客栈 可以找到任何你想要的女孩
You go to this hostel, you will have any girl you want.
她们为所有的外国人着迷
They go crazy for any foreigner.
你只要…
You just…
干她们
take them.
该死的
Fuck, man.
你就不能穿上裤子呆一会吗 北欧强盗
Can't you keep your Viking ass in your pants for, like, two seconds?
嘿 我只为你展示我的屁股
Hey, man, I shaved my ass just for you.
- 好了 - 还有我的北欧睾丸
- Okay, all right. - My Viking balls too.
好了 停下
Okay, stop.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我的女儿
My daughter.
她想她的爸爸 爸爸也想她
She miss her daddy, and Daddy miss her.
好 很正常 兄弟 这很不错
Yeah, no problem, dude, it's cool.
- 萨斯琦娅 - 很可爱
- Saskia. - Cute.
- 她真可爱 - 没错 她真是个小美人儿
- She's adorable. - She's a little cutie, yeah.
这是辛妮拉 我的女儿
This is Svanhildur, my daughter.
- 真漂亮 - 6岁了
- Very pretty. - She's 6.
今年开始上学了
She's starting school this year.
等等 你有一个女儿？
Wait, you have a daughter?
是的 当然 我的朋友 我已经结婚8年了
Yeah, of course, my horse. I was married for eight years.
哦 是么
Okay. All right.
- 你们在度假吗？- 是的 我们在背包旅行
- You are on vacation? - Yeah, we're backpacking.
我们的下一站是布拉迪斯拉发
Our next stop is Bratislava.
- 怎么了？- 斯洛伐克
- What? - Slovakia.
你们会喜欢那里的
You will like it.
娱乐场 女孩
Casino, girls.
只要付钱 你可以做任何事情
You can pay to do anything.
任何事
Anything.
- 那里女孩怎么样？- 非常漂亮
- How are the girls? - Very beautiful.
她们会爱上你们的 像你们这样潇洒的美国人
They will love you. Handsome American like you.
潇洒的恶魔吧 他是挺帅的
Handsome devil. He is handsome.
真是 有毛病 真是挺奇怪的
That's… That's awkward. That's awkward.
这也很奇怪
That's awkward too.
- 你需要个叉子吗？- 不 不 不
- You need a fork there, chief? - No, no, no.
我更喜欢用手
I prefer to use my hands.
我相信
I believe…
人们已经失去了他们和食物之间的联系
people have lost their relationship with food.
他们不认为
They do not think:
这是一些为了添饱我们的肚子 而失去了他们的生命的东西
"This is something who gave its life so I would not go hungry."
我喜欢和为我而死的东西接触
I like to have a connection with something that died for me.
我更能欣赏它
I appreciate it more.
哦 我是个素食者
Well, I'm vegetarian.
我是吃荤的
And I am a meat - eater.
这是人类的本性
It's human nature.
但我也是人 这不是我的本性
Well, I'm human, and it's not in my nature.
告诉我 你的本性是什么？
Tell me, what is your nature?
别摸！别他妈的碰我
Don't touch! Don't fucking touch me!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
对不起
Excuse me.
真是变态
Fucking freak.
上帝
Jesus.
爱德华沙拉刚才摸了乔希
Edward Saladhands just groped Josh.
老兄 你终于勾引到了他 真可怕
Dude, you finally hooked up. That's awesome.
是的 真他妈的高兴
Yeah, that's fucking hilarious.
或许我们可以参观一些工厂
Or we could visit some factories.
一定很有趣
Should be cool.
在这个地区
In this area…
我们为斯洛伐克制造塑料产品
we make plastic for Slovakia.
是吗？
Is that so?
看这个
Look at this.
- 真漂亮 是吧？- 这就是那个该死的客栈？
- Nice, eh? - This is a fucking hostel?
真他妈的棒
Holy shit.
你可以拥有他 我吓得要命
You can have that, man. I'm too scared.
嘿 嘿 有人来了
Hey, hey. The party has arrived.
- 你从郁闷中被解救了 - 让我猜猜
- You are saved from boredom. - Let me guess.
你一定是摇摆王
You must be the King of the Swing.
你用摇摆王的名字预定的？
You made a reservation under "King of the Swing"?
- 是的 当然 我的朋友 - 抱歉
- Yeah, of course, my horse. - I'm sorry.
- 他还放不大开 - 可以看得出来
- He doesn't get out of his cage much. - I can see that.
这是你们的钥匙
Here are your keys.
你们把护照放在柜台
You leave your passports at the desk.
是我13岁时照的 我有点像爱斯基摩人
That was taken when I was like 13. I was kind of husky.
可是现在不像了 你看呢？
Not anymore, though, you know?
你们有私人房间吗？我们很可能会需要
Do you have any private rooms? We're probably gonna need them.
这里的房间都是半私用的 所以你们可能会有室友
The rooms are semiprivate, so you will have roommates.
舍友？值得高兴哈
Roommates, huh? That's gay.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 哦 天啊 - 没事
- Oh, my God. - It's okay.
这个房间是你们的 我们要去温泉浴了
The room is yours. We are going to the spa.
你们应该来
You should come.
温泉
Spa.
哦 不错
Jugs.
- 嘿 - 你好
- Hey. - Hello.
哦 天啊
Oh, Jesus.
- 你好 嘿 - 你好
- Hi. Hey. - Hi.
你好么？
How you doing?
真高兴可以展示我的身体
I'm so happy I shaved my balls.
什么？我在冰岛有着最光滑的睾丸
What? I have the smoothest balls in Iceland.
- 你们想看吗？- 不 不 不 你别 可以了
- You wanna see? - No, no, no, you're not… I'm good.
把你的那玩意儿拿开 简直让我毛骨悚然
Put your anteater away, it's totally creepy.
- 你不是从冰岛来的吧？- 不 不 美国
- You're not from Iceland, no? - No. Fuck, no. American.
不像他 我生下来就割过包皮了
Yeah, unlike him, I had my foreskin removed at birth.
我在谈论保健学么？
Hygiene and… Am I talking?
- 我是乔希 - 纳塔利亚
- I'm Josh. - Natalya.
- 这是斯维特拉娜 - 你好
- And this is Svetlana. - Hi.
你好 我是 帕克斯顿
Hi, I'm Paxton.
- 这是欧利 - 摇摆王
- And this is Oli. - The King of the Swing.
你好
Hello.
对着这个屁股 永远不会变老
Face on the ass. Never gets old.
天啊
Jesus.
你们这些女孩都来自哪儿？
So where are you girls from?
我来自意大利 但是我的父母是俄罗斯人
I'm from Italy, but my parents are Russian.
布拉格
Prague.
布拉格很美 卡夫卡
Prague's cool. Kafka.
纳塔利亚
So, Natalya…
- 恩？- 你是俄罗斯人 是吗？
- Yeah? - You're Russian, eh?
哦 我的天 看 那有好多女孩
Oh, my God. Look, there are too many girls.
- 真是好极了 - 是
- This is awesome. - Yes.
我的意思是 我上大三 她上大二
I mean, I was a senior, you know, she was a junior…
后来我毕业了 你知道 这感觉有点奇怪
and then I graduated, and it was weird, you know.
我想说 我完全忘记她了 这样很好
I mean, I'm totally over it. It's… You know, it's cool.
不错
It's okay.
看 维拉 在这里
Look, Vala is here.
- 谁？- 维拉 是前台的 维拉
- Who? - Vala, from front desk. Vala.
- 没错 欧利 - 嘿 我告诉过你
- All right, Oli. - Hey, I told you, man.
我是摇摆王
I'm the King of the Swing.
走 我们去跳舞吧
Come, let's dance.
- 你不介意我吸烟吧？- 不
- Does the cigarette bother you? - No, it's…
我拿远点
I put away.
没事 我
It's fine, I…
我出去呼吸点新鲜空气
I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
我一会会回来的 好吗？
But I'll be back, okay?
香烟
Cigarette.
你不觉得你太小了吗？
Aren't you a little young?
- 美金 - 什么？
- Dollar. - What?
美金
Dollar.
- 美金 - 给你
- Dollar. - Here you go.
在这里 大部分犯罪都是小孩子做的
Here, children commit the most crime.
他们不在乎 他们会袭击任何人
They don't care. They will attack anyone.
- 你还好吧？- 是的 谢谢
- You're okay? - Yeah, yeah. Thank you.
嘿 我请你喝点饮料吧
Hey, let me buy you a drink.
- 真的？- 是啊
- Yeah? - Yeah.
嘿 乔希
Hey, Josh.
同性恋佬
Faggot.
去陪你的朋友吧 我没事
Go with your friends. It's okay.
我对早些时候发生的事情感到抱歉
I wanted to say sorry about earlier.
我反应的太激烈了
About the way I reacted.
我们还是朋友？
We cool?
我在你的年龄也会做出同样的事情的
I would have done the same thing at your age.
这不容易
It's not easy…
但是根据我的经验
but from my experience…
成家对我来说是个正确的选择
choosing to have a family was the right choice for me.
现在我有我的小女儿
Now I have my little girl…
她对我来说比世界上任何事都重要
who means more to me than anything in the world.
但是你们应该
But you should do…
你们做任何事情都没有错
whatever's right for you.
抱歉 现在轮到我了
Excuse me, it's my turn now.
我们应该在那里和他们一起干吗？
Should we be doing this with them there?
哦 没关系
Yeah, it's okay.
哦 宝贝 乔希 把他让给我吧
Yeah, baby. Josh, give it to me, baby.
好的好的 不要
Okay, all right. Okay, stop!
- 好了 - 快点 大男孩
- All right. - Come on, big boy.
- 我们去温泉 - 温泉
- We go to spa. - Spa.
温泉 温泉 温泉 在变干净的时候其实是脏的
Spa, spa, spa. Being dirty while getting clean.
再见
Bye.
任务完成了
Mission accomplished.
你记得在嘴唇上挂东西的阿姆斯特丹孩子吗？
You know that Amsterdam kid with the thing on his lip?
我要给他一封诚挚的感谢信
I'm gonna send him a really nice thank - you note.
安静
Be quiet.
他们正在一起洗澡呢
They're showering together.
该死的 我们不要离开这了
Shit, man. We're never leaving here.
我猜欧利还没回来呢
I guess Oli's not back yet.
没有 老兄 他很可能把那个前台女孩带回家了
No, dude, he probably took that desk girl home.
早饭时我们会看见他的
We'll see him at breakfast.
- 名字？- 欧利·艾里克森 237
- What's the name? - Oli Ericson, 237.
我们怎么能看得懂这些没有字幕的节目啊？
How are we supposed to understand this without subtitles?
他妈的同性恋
Fucking gay.
哦 他今早退房了
Yeah, he checked out this morning.
你是说他拿着护照出去了？
You mean he took his passport to go out?
不 上面只是说他今早退房了
No, it say he checked out this morning.
- 今早什么时候？- 我不知道确切时间
- When this morning? - I don't know exact time.
明天我会查明白的
I could find out tomorrow.
嘿 欧利 我是 帕克斯 你还和那个女人在一起吗？
Hey, Oli, it's Pax. Are you still with that chick?
我能留个便条给他吗？
Can I leave a note in case he comes back?
好的 没问题
Okay, cool. Yeah.
好了
All right.
他很可能还和维拉在一起
He's probably still with Vala.
如果她打电话给我 我会打给你 好吗？
When she call me, I call you, okay?
好的
Okay.
- 我们回头见？- 好的
- We see you later, right? - Yeah.
好
Okay.
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye - bye. - Bye.
欧利 嘿 还是我 我们要进城去了 打电话给我们
Oli, hey, it's me again. We're gonna go into town, so call us.
玩得开心 该死的又是语音邮件
You're gay. Damn voice mail again.
- 嗨 嗨 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi! Hi! Hi! - Hi.
你们的朋友
Your friend.
- 究竟怎么了？- 你们的朋友 我的朋友
- What the hell? - Your friend, my friend.
说什么？
What does that say?
再见 你们的朋友
Sayonara. Your friend.
什么 他们走了？一起走的？
What, they left? Like, together?
这讲不通啊 欧利一点都不喜欢亚洲女孩
That doesn't make any sense. Oli doesn't even like Asian girls.
我是说 别介意 但是
I mean, no offense, but…
她什么时候发给你的？
When did she send this to you?
这张图 今天？
This picture. Today?
可以帮个忙 把这张图发到我手机上来吗？
Could you do me a favor and send this picture to my phone?
这张图
This picture.
这水看起来真他妈的冷
That water looks fucking cold.
如果掉进去 90秒就会死的
You know, if you fell in, you'd die in 90 seconds.
伙计 我和你说过 我8岁时看着一个女孩淹死的事吗？？
Dude, did I tell you I saw a girl drown when I was 8?
- 在哪里？- 密歇根湖
- Where? - Lake Michigan.
很混乱 那个小女孩大概4 5岁的样子
It was fucked up, man. This little girl, probably 4 or 5.
我看着她的眼睛 里面有一些神秘的东西
We made eye contact, which was a weird thing, you know…
她朝我大叫 让我帮助她
and she was yelling for me to help her.
是么？你怎么做的？
Yeah? What did you do?
我跑向救生员
I ran to the lifeguard,
当时她正忙着和他男朋友讲话
who was busy talking to her boyfriend at the time…
我大声叫 那里有个女孩要淹死了
and I yelled, you know, "There's this girl drowning."
她从救生塔上看不见她 她很可能觉得我在撒谎
And she couldn't see her. Probably thought I was making it up.
一秒钟以后
And then a second later
我们都可以听见那恐怖的尖叫声
all you could hear was this horrible screaming.
那是女孩的妈妈 朋友
It was that little girl's mother, dude.
她的孩子死了
Her kid was dead.
- 天啊 - 在这以后好多年我都会做恶梦
- Jesus. - I had nightmares for years after that.
我每晚都在那个母亲的尖叫声中惊醒
I mean, I'd wake up every fucking night hearing that mother scream.
我只是
I just…
我只是觉得我可以做的更多
I just felt like I could have done more.
你做的没错 不然可能变成两条人命
You did the right thing. Could've been a double drowning.
我那时可不这么想
Yeah, well, I didn't see it that way at the time.
我想到的就是那个小女孩死了
All I knew was this little girl was dead
那个母亲的生活也被毁掉了
and her mother's life was ruined.
你怎么想起这事情了？
What makes you think of this now?
泡泡糖
Bubble gum.
- 抱歉 孩子 - 不 不 给他点
- Sorry, kid. - No, no. Give him some.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
这些该死的小孩很危险
These fucking kids are dangerous.
嘿 欧利
Hey, Oli.
- 嘿 欧利 - 嘿
- Hey, Oli. - Hey.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿 欧利 嘿 - 欧利
- Hey, Oli. Hey! - Oli!
今天真是你的幸运日 乔希
It's your lucky day, Josh.
博物馆
A museum.
这是怎么挂起来的？
How's it hanging?
- 什么？- 该死
- What the fuck? - Holy shit.
- 他抓住你了 - 哦 真滑稽
- He got you. - Yeah, that's hilarious.
好了
Okay.
嘿 欧利
Hey, Oli.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
什么事？
Excuse me?
对不起 我把你当成另一个人了
I'm sorry, I thought you were someone else.
我不是
Well, I'm not.
你从哪里弄到的这件夹克？
Where did you get that jacket?
- 嘿 我在和你说话呢 - 把你的脏手从我身上拿开
- Hey, I'm talking to you, man. - Get your fucking hands off me.
这是我的夹克
This is my jacket.
欧利发来的
It's from Oli.
我回家了？
"I go home"?
我不知道 也许他的电池没电了
I don't know, maybe his battery died.
嘿 卡纳 你什么时候走？
Hey, Kana, when are you leaving?
对不起 你什么时候离开？
I'm sorry. When are you going away?
明天 我走
Tomorrow, I go.
好的 明天我们也走
Okay, because we may go too.
你想和我们一起赶火车么？去火车站？
Do you wanna go to the train with us? To the train station?
明天 火车？
Tomorrow, train?
对 对
Yeah, yeah.
- 你好 乔希 - 嘿
- Hello, Josh. - Hey.
- 嘿 - 来 我们去迪斯科？
- Hey. - Come, we go for disco?
事实上 我只想找到我的朋友
Actually, I just wanna find my friend
从这个该死的地方离开
and get the fuck out of here.
好吧 那一会见
Okay, we'll see you.
嘿 等一下 我们一会就出去
Hey, guys, hold up a sec. We'll be right out.
好的
Okay.
- 乔希 来这里 - 好 怎么了？
- Josh, come here, dude. - Yeah, what?
欧利失踪并不是她们的责任 所以不要这样对她们
It's not their fault Oli disappeared, so stop acting like it is.
- 我觉得他在耍我们 - 我也很生气
- I'm annoyed he'd ditch us. - I'm pissed too.
但是我们不是在美国
But we're not in America.
我的意思是 人们相遇 然后分开 这没什么好说的
I mean, people meet each other and split without saying shit.
这就是这里的人们的方式
It's just how they do it over here.
也许我们觉得我们了解欧利 但是我们并不真正了解他
As well as we may think we know Oli, we don't really know him.
他可能和那个女孩去了某个地方
He could've gone somewhere with that girl.
妈的 他也许在冰岛 这家伙有个女儿
Fuck, maybe he's in Iceland. The guy's got a daughter.
所以我们在这有两个选择
So let's look at our options.
我们可以多和那些女孩鬼混一天
We can A, fuck these girls one more night
然后到巴塞罗那去
and then head to Barcelona…
或者直接到巴塞罗那去
or B, not fuck them, then head to Barcelona anyway.
考虑一下吧
Think about it.
我回去继续学我的律师 而你继续写你的论文
When I'm studying for the bar and you're writing your thesis…
这才使我们需要想的事情
this is the shit we're gonna think about.
好吧 他不再露面 这是他的问题
Okay. All right, he doesn't show up, it's his problem.
- 这是他的问题 - 没错
- It's his problem. - All right.
没错
All right.
嘿 卡娜 想和我们一起去迪斯科吗？
Hey, Kana, you wanna go to the disco with us?
迪斯科？跳舞？
You know, disco? Dancing?
不？
No?
乔希？
Josh?
- 我要回去了 - 你还好吧？
- I'm gonna go back. - Are you okay?
我有点累了
I'm, like… I'm tired.
事实上 我有点头痛
Actually, I have, like, a headache.
如果你需要 我可以和你一起回去
If you want, I will go with you.
不 不 不 我们回房间再见
No, no, no, I'll just see you back at the room.
再见
Goodbye.
废物
Fucking pussy.
- 乔希 - 维拉
- Josh. - Vala.
你看起来不大好
You don't look well.
- 不 我 - 我帮你
- No, I - Here, let me help you.
我有点不舒服
I feel sick.
在哪里？欧利在哪里？
Where is? Where is Oli?
你需要休息
You need rest.
厕所在哪里？
Where's the restroom?
过了吧台 就在后面
Past the bar, in the back.
你们要什么？
You guys cool?
- 伏特加红色公牛 - 伏特加红色公牛 加水
- Vodka Red Bull. - Vodka Red Bull, danke.
好
Yeah.
嘿
Hey!
开门
Open the door.
妈的
Oh, fuck.
怎么了
What the f…?
妈的
Oh, fuck.
什么？你是谁？
What? Who are you?
怎么了？我他妈的在那？
What the f…? Where the fuck am I?
这他妈的是什么？
What the fuck is this shit?
不 不 妈的 不 不 不
Please, please Fuck. Please, please, please…
我没对你怎样过 怎么回事
I didn't fucking do shit to you, what the fuck!
不 不 什么？
Please, please, what the…?
不 不 先生 快停下 不
Please, no, sir. Please fucking stop. Please!
怎么回事？
What the fuck?
不 我什么事都没做过
Please, I didn't fucking do anything.
怎么回事？
What the fuck?
怎么回事？太荒谬了
What the fuck? This is such fucking bullshit.
这他妈的是什么？
What the fuck is this?
什么？不 不 不要
What? No! No, please don't…!
什么？不 不 不要 不 不
What the…? No, no, fucking don't you… No, no!
哦 我的天 不 不 哦 天啊
Oh, my God, no, no! Oh, my fucking God!
哦 天 不 不 不 不
Oh, my God! No, no, no, no!
哦 求你了 怎么回事？
Oh, please. What the fuck?
不 不 不 不 妈的 不
No, no, no, no, fuck! No!
妈的 哦 妈的
Fuck! Oh, fuck!
你
You.
为什么？
Why?
我总是想作一个外科医生
I always wanted to be a surgeon…
但是我没有通过
but the boards wouldn't pass me.
知道为什么么？
Can you guess why?
你看？
You see?
所以我开始做生意
So I went into business…
但是生意很无聊
but business is so boring.
你买东西 然后卖掉 你赚钱 然后花掉
You buy things, you sell them. You make money, you spend money.
这是什么样的生活？
What kind of life is that?
外科医生
A surgeon…
在他的手中掌握着生命的精髓
he holds the very essence of life in his hands.
你的生命
Your life.
他触摸它
He touches it.
他与它有联系
He has a relationship with it.
他是生命的一部分
He's part of it.
求你了 让我走吧 求你了
Please, please. Just let me go, please.
你想走吗？
You want to go?
真的想走吗？
Is that what you want?
哦 天啊
Oh, my God!
妈的 哦 他妈的
Fuck! Oh, fuck!
你可以走了
You are free to go.
哦 妈的 不
Oh, fuck. No!
不 不 妈的 不 妈的
No. No, fuck. No, fuck…
求你了 我有钱 我他妈的都给你
Please, I have money. I'll fucking pay you.
十倍 二倍 你想要什么都行
Ten times, two times, whatever you want…
- 付给我？- 是
- Pay me? - Yes.
没人付钱给我
No one is paying me.
事实上 我向他们付钱
In fact, I am the one paying them.
放松 放松 兄弟
Relax. Relax, bro.
哦 该死的
Oh, shit.
- 237 - 237
- Two thirty-seven, please. - Two three seven.
你没退房吗？
Didn't you check out?
没 还没有
No, not yet.
还没有
Not yet.
- 这是你的包？- 对
- This your bag? - Yeah.
女佣把它拿到这里的 你已经退房了
The maid brought it here. You're checked out.
- 我还没有啊 - 这上面记得
- I didn't check out. - It says.
今天早上退的
It happened this morning.
胡说 有人留条子给我吗？
This is bullshit. Did somebody leave a note?
因为我他妈的还没有退房 伙计
Because I didn't fucking check out, dude.
没有 只有这个包 如果这是个错误
No, man, just this bag. If it's a mistake…
是的 这确实是个错误 我们他妈的需要另一个房间
Yeah, it's definitely a mistake. We need a fucking room.
冷静点 你在度假那
Chill out, man. You're on vacation.
嘿 这不是有个日本女孩在休息厅里等人吗？
Hey, was there a Japanese girl waiting in the lobby for somebody?
不 她们今早走了
No, think they left this morning.
哦
Yeah.
抱歉 朋友
I'm sorry, dude.
对不起 抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry. Excuse me.
没事 我们正要去温泉
It's okay. We are going to the spa.
和我们一起吗？
You will join us?
你应该来
You should come.
嘿 乔希 收到我的留言就打电话给我
Hey, Josh, call me soon as you get this, man.
我被锁在俱乐部里了 所以晚了
I got locked in that club. It was retarded, dude.
我现在在客栈
I'm at the hostel.
斯维特拉娜
Svetlana!
嘿
Hey!
你这个小兔崽子
You little fucker.
天
Jesus.
在客栈等你的朋友们
Wait at hostel for your friends.
无论如何他们都会去那里找你的
They will look for you there no matter what.
好 我知道 但是 我的朋友乔希是那种
Yeah, I know. But, see, my friend Josh is the kind of guy who…
他是不会连张便条都不留就退房的
He just wouldn't check out without so much as leaving a note, you know.
他是很负责的人
He's the responsible one.
是的 但是也许 他担心他的东西被偷了那
Yeah, but maybe he worried his belongings get stolen…
所以他离开的时候把东西带走了
so he take them when he go out.
也许有人把他的便条放错了
Someone misplace if he leaves note.
这很正常
It is not uncommon.
是的 我还能做什么呢？
Yeah, well, is there anything else that I can do?
现在没什么事情
There's nothing right now.
我们有他的照片
We have his picture…
如果我们看见他 或者他被送来 或者发生了其他的事情
if we see him, or he is picked up, or something happen…
我们会到客栈和你联系的 好吗？
we contact you at hostel, yeah?
好的
Okay.
你从哪里来？
Where are you from?
加利福尼亚
California.
你离家够远的
You are so far from home.
帕克斯顿 来 喝一杯
Paxton. Come, have a drink.
你好 美国先生
Hello, Mr. American.
- 你收到我的信息了吗？- 哪一条？
- Did you get my messages? - Which one?
有很多条
There are so many.
我给你打回去 但是是个小孩接的
I call you back, but child answer.
哦 我知道
Yeah, I know.
你看见乔希了吗？
Have you seen Josh?
用英语 好吗？
In English, please.
他和你的朋友一起
He is with your friend…
摇摆王
the King of the Swing.
- 他和欧利一起 - 你昨晚为什么离开了？
- He's with Oli. - Why you leave last night?
你没听见我的信息吗？我被锁在一件储藏室里了
Did you not listen to my messages? I got locked in a storage room.
我不知道 我觉得不舒服 然后昏倒了
I don't know, I got sick and passed out.
- 什么？- 她说你去找其他女孩了
- What? - She said you met another girl.
我的朋友在哪里？
Where are my friends?
艺术展
The art show.
- 你是说像一间博物馆么？- 不 不 不
- You mean like a museum? - No, no, no.
不是博物馆 他们去了 你们怎么说 为艺术家办的
Not museum. They went… How you say, for artist?
- 展览 - 艺术家的展览
- Exhibit. - Exhibit for artist.
不 这不可能
No, that doesn't make any sense.
为什么？哪里不对了？
Why? What is wrong?
好吧 他们没留下便条 也没打电话或者干别的
Well, they didn't leave a note. They didn't call or do anything.
他们让我们告诉你
They tell us to tell you.
好 但是我一整天都在给他们打电话
Yeah, but I tried calling them all day.
是 但是他们的电话电池没电了 他们也没有
Yes, but their phone, the battery die and they do not have…
你们怎么说 为了充电？
How you say, for electricity?
转换器 好 不管怎样 艺术展在哪里
Converter. Okay, whatever, where is this art show…
我要去
because I wanna go.
- 喝一杯 - 我不想喝
- Have a drink. - I don't want a drink.
没问题吧？我想看看艺术
All right? I wanna see some art.
好？我们可以走了吗？
Okay? So can we go?
你不去吗？
You're not going?
我看过展览了
I've seen this show.
要香口胶么？
You want gum?
不
No.
你可真不幸
Too bad for you.
我们到了
We are here.
你要来么还是怎么样？
Are you coming or what?
请问 请问
Excuse me. Excuse me.
这里面什么样？
How is it in there?
小心
Be careful.
为什么这样说？
Why is that?
你会花光你所有的钱
You could spend all your money…
在那里面
in there.
多少钱？
How much is it?
对你免费
For you, free.
那边
There.
这就是展览吗？
That's the show?
是的
Yes.
- 什么？- 没什么
- What? - Nothing.
你这么严肃 严肃的美国先生
You're so serious, Mr. Serious American.
你这个妓女
You fucking whore.
婊子
You fucking bitch.
You fucking bitch!
我从你身上赚了很多钱
I get a lot of money for you…
这已经可以使你成为我的婊子了
and that make you my bitch.
妈的 放开我
Fuck. Get the fuck off me!
妈的
This is fucked!
妈的 放开我
Get the fuck off me!
放开我
妈的
Fuck.
讲话
Talk.
说话 说啊
Talk. Speak.
你他妈的让我说什么？
What the fuck do you want me to say?
美国人
American.
不 不 等等
No. No, wait!
我他妈的不是美国人
I'm not fucking American!
我他妈的不是 看看我 我他妈的不是美国人
I'm not fucking… Look at me. I'm not fucking American.
美国人
American.
请问 这他妈的是什么？
Please, what the fuck is this?
让我走 求你们了
Let me go. Please.
我保证不会告诉别人的
I promise I won't tell anybody.
让我走
Just please let me go.
不要 不要
Don't. Don't.
不要 求你了
Please don't.
Don't, please.
天
God.
哦 住手
Oh, please, stop!
住手 住手
Please stop it. Please stop it.
我知道你不想这样做
I know you don't wanna do this.
不要这样
Please don't do this.
妈的
Fuck.
该死
Oh, shit.
怎么回事？
What the fuck?
你在想什么？
What do you think?
我看起来怎么样？
How do I look?
我感觉好像是屠夫或者外科医生 或者狗屁不如
I feel like a butcher or a surgeon or some shit,
明白我的意思吗？
know what I mean?
我觉得这件事非常可笑
I feel fucking ridiculous in this thing,
但是我猜你需要这样 不是吗？
but I guess you need it, huh?
好 我要告诉你一些事
Yeah. I'll tell you something…
- 对不起 对不起 - 等一下
- Excuse me. Excuse me. - Wait a sec.
做的怎么样？
How was it?
还好
Good.
好了 讨厌 该死的
Well, goddamn, motherfucker,
就这么点钱 已经够好了 狗屎
for this money, it better be. Shit.
你找的什么？当地人？
What did you go for, a local?
什么 欧洲人？
What, European?
- 美国人 - 美国人？
- American. - An Amer…?
那是个婊子 挥金如土 妈的 我喜欢这样
Ain't that a bitch. Big spender. I fucking… I love it.
我真他妈的喜欢这样 你知道他们怎么和我说么？
I just fucking love that shit. You know what they got for me?
他们说他们在准备一些特别的
They told me they lined up something special.
为这事我他妈的已经等了将近一周了
I've been waiting almost a week for this shit.
总共50 她最好值这个价
For 50 grand, she better be worth it.
不过这应该真的很刺激 对吗？
But it's supposed to be a real rush, right?
就像 他们告诉我的 这真他妈的爽 对吗？
It's like… They told me it's like a real fucking rush, right?
来这里
Come here.
我去过全世界 我什么地方都去过
I've been all over the world. You know, I've been everywhere.
底线就是 小姑娘的阴道
And the bottom line is, pussy's pussy.
你知道 每一个脱衣舞夜总会 每一个妓院 每一个
You know, every strip club, every whorehouse, every…
都他妈是一样的
It's all the same shit.
两天前我才干过一个女孩
I just fucked a girl two days ago,
我现在都不记得她乳头的颜色了
I don't even remember the color of her tits.
但是 这是你永远难忘的 对吗？
But this, this is something you never forget, right?
对吗？
Right?
- 永远难忘 - 永远难忘 对
- Never. - Never, right.
我给你看点东西 相当不错 来看看
Let me show you something. Pretty sweet. Check this out.
你觉得怎么样？快点 让我看看你的
What do you think of this? Come on, let me see yours.
快点 让我看看你的 我们都在同一家俱乐部
Come on, let me see yours. We're all in the same club.
我马上就出去 伙计
I'll be out in a second, guy.
能问你点私人问题吗？你介意吗？
Can I ask you something personal? Do you mind?
你是怎么做的？
How'd you do it?
你是慢慢做
Did you do it real slow…
还是迅速做完？
or did you just get it over with right away?
这正是我要枪的原因
That's why I asked for the fucking gun.
因为我只想快点干完
Because I just wanted to fucking do it quick.
我只是想干完事
I just wanted to get it over with.
不过现在我认为也许我想感觉它 明白么？
But now I'm thinking maybe I wanna feel it, you know?
我想享受这件事
I wanna fucking feel that shit.
我不知道该怎么做
So I don't know what to…
我在想 你觉得我应该怎么做？
I'm thinking What do you think I should do?
- 快点结束 - 快点结束
- Make it quick. - Make it quick.
是
Yes.
对 那是 不 去他妈的
Yeah, that's… No, fuck that shit.
妈的 操他妈的美国人 伙计
Fuck this, too fucking American, dude.
这方法太他妈老套了
I'm going fucking old school.
谁要这个？妈的
Who wants this, motherfucker?
谁要这个？快点 妈的
Who wants this shit? Come on, motherfucker.
把它拿过来
Bring it.
嘿 伙计
Hey, buddy.
他妈的回你自己屋里去 这个我交过钱了
Get your own fucking room. I paid for this.
你是什么 你他妈是聋子吗？
What are you, fucking deaf?
卡娜
Kana.
- 哦 天 - 你要我做什么 卡娜？
- Oh, my God. - What do you want me to do, Kana?
什么？我不明白你在说什么 什么？
What? I don't understand what you're saying. What?
该死 抱歉 抱歉 别动 别动
Fuck. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Hold still. Hold still.
- 妈的 哦 天啊 天啊 - 不 不
- Fuck. Oh, God. God. - No. No!
- 该死 - 不
- Shit. - No!
对不起 对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
妈的
Fuck!
我们就要离开这该死的鬼地方了 卡娜
We're gonna get the fuck out of here, Kana.
挪一下那该死的卡车
Move this fucking truck!
妈的
Fuck.
我们已经差不多到了
We're almost there.
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
哦 不
Oh, no.
妈的
Fuck.
卡娜
Kana.
来这里
Come here.
不 不 卡娜 卡娜
No. No, Kana. Kana.
不 卡娜
No, Kana.
不 谢谢 我更喜欢用手
No, thank you. I prefer to use my hands.
我相信人们已经失去了 他们和食物之间的联系
I believe people have lost their relationship with food.
他们不认为：
They do not think:
这是一些为了添饱我们的肚子 而失去了他们的生命的东西
"This is something who gave its life so I would not go hungry."
我喜欢和为我而死的东西接触
I like to have a connection with something that died for me.
哦 天啊
Oh, Jesus.
恶魔
Goddamn!
妈的
Fucker.